elfsight.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy - Elfsight

### 1\. Introduction

When you use Elfsight site and products, you trust us with your information. This Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand what data we collect, why we collect it, and what we do with it. This is important; we hope you will take time to read it carefully.

### 2\. Information we collect

We collect non-Identifying information we get from your use of our site and products. This information includes your IP address, interactions with the site, referring URL, browser, operating system, cookie information, usage, data transferred and Internet Service Provider, Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party such as your wireless provider, this information alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

### 3\. Use of your information

We will never sell, transfer or give your information to a third party without your permission. However, you agree that we may use your information:

  * To enhance or improve our users’ experiences.
  * To contact you and to respond to inquiries.

Additionally, we may give your information to law enforcement if we are compelled to by a court order, if there has been a violation of any US laws, EU laws or if a violation of Privacy Policy has occurred.

### 4\. Cookies

We use cookies to save your preferences and to remember your shopping cart. For this reason, you must have cookies enabled in your browser to use our site. Additionally, some or all of our cookies may be accessible by third parties.

### 5\. Law Enforcement

You agree that we may disclose your information to authorities if compelled to by a court order. Additionally, you agree that we may disclose your information if we reasonably believe that you have violated a US law or Privacy Policy or if we believe that a third party is at risk of bodily harm. In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either. We may also proactively report you and release your information without receiving any request to third parties where we believe that it is proper to do so for legal reasons, such as instances where we believe your publications violate any law of the United States or any other country having jurisdiction over us, our site, products. You release us from any damages that may arise from or relate to the release of your information to a request from law enforcement agencies or private litigants. We may release your information under the conditions listed in this paragraph whether it is to individuals or entities and to any state or Federal authorities within the United States, or elsewhere.

### 6\. Third parties

Elfsight may post links to third party websites on our site or products, which may include information that we have no control over. When accessing a third party site through our site or products, you acknowledge that you are aware that these third party websites are not screened for privacy or security issues by us, and you release us from any liability for the conduct of these third party websites.

Please be aware that this Privacy Policy, and any other policies in place, in addition to any amendments, does not create rights enforceable by third parties. Elfsight bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any advertiser or third party website. You must review their Terms of Service and Privacy to understand how their information collection practices work.

### 7\. Security Measures

We use SSL Certificates and vulnerability scanning to enhance the security of our site. However, we make no guarantees as to the security or privacy of your information. It is in our interest to keep our website secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, routine credit checks, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security and privacy threats.

### 8\. When this Privacy Policy applies

Our Privacy Policy applies to the site https://elfsight.com/ and products offered on it, but excludes services that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this Privacy Policy.

### 9\. Changes

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes).
